有的人要干活
费斯特公司　拉尔夫·贝克尔
总是这样
可笑的是 他们在那个鬼地方什么都不说
从不告诉你需要做什么 之后却怪你不干活 太可笑了
要我教你怎么做吗
慕尼黑  德国
“把德国还给德国人”　曼弗雷德·费斯特
晚上好 拉尔夫 又迟到了啊
天啊 抽烟可没好处
不用你说
新包啊 拉尔夫
没事吧
埃利亚斯·费斯特接手管理费斯特出版集团
拉尔夫 晚上好
今天有谁来过
只有费斯特先生和詹妮弗
他们有说我需要从哪开始吗
没告诉过我
总是这样
费斯特公司
你没关吸尘器
重大变故的发生只是时间问题
有枪手 快逃
饶命啊 别开枪
风雷达
改编自弗雷德里克·福赛斯的小说
由罗南·班尼特为电视创作
由克里斯托弗・霍尔制作
由布莱恩・柯克执导
豺狼的日子
第一季 第一集
下一届德国总理热门候选人 曼弗雷德·费斯特...
将在今天上午去医院看望他儿子 埃利亚斯
埃利亚斯昨晚遭遇了暗杀
...评论员认为 这与曼弗雷德的反移民政治倾向有关...
关掉广播
好的
第一次电话里说情况挺乐观的
The first call was pretty positive,
但今早 医生说他们要再次给他的腿做手术
but then this morning, the surgeon said they need to operate again on the leg.
哭有什么用 不 我是在认真的和你说
我们赶在手术前到医院
We're on our way there now before they prep him.
你这样能帮到埃利亚斯吗 拜托你振作一点
好的 再见
OK. Bye.
他母亲哭得像个孩子
她总是情绪失控
需要让办公室的人送花吗 或者送卡片
送点...温馨的
不行 不能是温馨的
我们可不想引起什么误会 那就送点...
...能平复她心情的东西吧
预计三分钟后到达
收到
不好意思... 处理点公事
你想对关于乌勒·达格·查尔斯的最新报道发表评论吗
可以拒绝表态 英国媒体问的
英国媒体 好吧
For the British? Well...
乌勒·达格·查尔斯 真名苏莱曼
This man, Ulle Dag Charles, real name Suleiman,
他不喜欢用真名是有原因的
which he prefers not to use, understandably,
他是个哗众取宠的骗子
is an attention-seeking fraud.
每次他有新的软件要卖
Every time he has a new piece of software to sell,
都说软件能拯救世界
he promises it will save the world,
但他其实想毁灭世界
but all he wants to do is destroy it.
乌勒·达格·查尔斯背离了西方价值观
Ulle Dag Charles is a traitor to the West and its values.
反对法西斯费斯特　我们都是人 拒绝对穆斯林的煽动　拯救民主
这些趁人之危的混蛋
他们没有良知吗
费斯特 你这个法西斯
一群乌合之众
先生 请您留在车内
女士 您也一样
我们行动要快
候选人一下车 我们要在十秒内护送他进去
明白了吗
有枪手
检查我们东南侧的三十层大楼
枪手可能在十六或十七层
有炸弹
Bombe!
伦敦  英国
军情六处总部
刚刚拿到的 我就知道你想看
It's just come in. I knew you'd wanna see it.
俄罗斯的2000 MG
Russian 2000 MG.
这枪少见
Not something you see every day.
序列号被磨掉了
Hmm, the serial number's filed off.
恐怖分子也不傻
Well, terrorists aren't entirely stupid.
这么说 这枪是真的
So, is it the genuine article?
看着像真的
Yeah, looks like the real thing.
虽然现在巴西和埃及的仿制枪也不差
Although the Brazilian and Egyptian knock-offs are almost as good these days.
好枪
Very nice gun.
来看看是不是来自比利时的枪支贩卖商
Right, let's see if it's one of our Belgian dealers.
肯定还有一处刻有序列号
There's gotta be another one in here somewhere.
他们不傻
They're not always entirely stupid,
但也不怎么聪明
but they're not that smart either.
找到了
Bingo.
你看这个新闻了吗
Have you seen this?
这是在哪
Where is that?
德国
Germany.
纽伦堡  德国
这东西
That is an absolutely...
太棒了
beautiful thing.
我本来可以把它们寄给你
You know I could have shipped them to you and, er...
你就不必专程过来
saved you the journey.
错过这么难得的机会 不用了 谢谢
What a miss seeing all this? No, thank you.
天哪 这件东西可真别致
Christ, the Puzzle Ball's something special.
没错
Yes, it is.
但可惜不售卖
Sadly not for sale.
不过 我有一套漂亮的基拉尼藏品
However, I do have a beautiful Killarney set...
我可能会考虑转手
that I might be persuaded to part with.
-去看看  -跟我来
- Go on then. - This way.
天哪
Christ.
克拉斯纳先生 恕我直言
Herr Krasner, with the greatest respect...
我得走了 不然我会破产
I need to get out of here before I bankrupt myself.
科技企业家 乌勒·达格·查尔斯
Tech entrepreneur, Ulle Dag Charles,
-简称乌达查  -嗨
- or UDC as he prefers to be known... - Hey.
嗨
Hey.
-你还好吗  -我很好 你呢
- You alright? - Yeah, I'm good. How are you doing?
嗯
Yeah, I'm...
-很好  -要喝杯水吗
- Yeah. - Yeah. You want a glass?
不用了 我没事 谢谢
No, I'm good. Thank you.
名为资流 乌勒·达格·查尔斯 资流是个什么神秘的新软件
...he called River. Ulle Dag Charles, what is this mysterious new software, River?
资流是革命性技术
River is a revolutionary technology...
论文写的怎么样了
Er, how's the paper?
我终于想出了一个新标题
I finally came up with a new title for it, actually.
-对 -是吗 什么标题
- Yeah? - Yeah. What is it?
标题是 有争议的暴力与自我主宰
It's called, "Problematic Violences and Self-Authorship:
弥赛亚情结陷阱与悲剧命运
Traps of the Messianic and the Tragic."
谢谢
Thank you.
这标题是什么意思
What does it actually mean, though?
拜托 你懂枪 肯定知道是什么意思
Come on, you learned firearms, you know what it means.
贾思敏呢 在做作业吗
Where's Jasmine? Homework?
对 在做作业
Homework, exactly.
为什么你作为一个亿万富翁
Why is a man who is a founder member of the billionaire club
要和其他亿万富翁作对
turning against his fellow billionaires?
能看看费斯特谋杀案的新闻吗
Can we find something on the Fest killing, please?
拜托 这可是乌达查 你应该好好看才是
Come on, this is UDC. You should be all over this.
他有两亿四千万粉丝
He's got like 240 million followers.
-有人认为他是上帝  -对 他自己也是这么认为的
- Some people think he's God. - Yeah, including him.
-瞧瞧他这样子  -但他总是出人意料
- Look at him. - You never know with this guy, though.
我是说 要是这个软件真像他说的那样
I mean, if this software does what it's supposed to,
它能让我们看清所有钱款的来源和去向
it's gonna show us where all the big money's coming from and where it goes.
他要真能成功
Like, if he pulls this off,
那可太有趣了
this could get really interesting.
但现在不有趣 有人被暗杀了
But it's not interesting right now. Someone's been assassinated.
-我觉得有趣  -拜托 你能不能...
- It is to me. - Please. Can you ju...
不行 你不能一回家就...
No! Listen, you can't just come here...
- 给我遥控器  -行行行
Give me it. Come home... Fine, fine, fine.
拿去 真不给你老公面子
Take it. Wow, no respect for your husband, no?
多谢夸奖
Thank you.
突发新闻 民粹主义政客曼弗雷德·费斯特遭遇暗杀 引发全德震惊
警方通报说 费斯特被被一颗子弹击中
According to police sources, Fest was struck by a single bullet
子弹从远处射出
fired by a sniper from long range.
目前尚未确认
It's not yet confirmed if authorities
是否找到嫌疑人
have been able to locate a suspect or...
-妈 晚上好  -嗨 过得怎么样
- Evening, Mum. - Hi, how you doing?
-在学校过得怎么样  -不错
- How was school? - Good.
不错 不错
Good. Good.
你记得明晚有啥嘛
Do you remember what's happening tomorrow night?
记得
Yes.
家长会
Parent-teachers' evening.
对 我会去
Yes. I'm going to come.
-太棒了  -好吗
- Good. - Alright?
-好  -费斯特当时正要去圣伊丽莎白医院看望儿子埃利亚斯·费斯特
- OK. - ..was visiting his son, Elias Fest, at the Saint Elizabeth hospital,
埃利亚斯前一天受伤了
who had suffered injuries the day prior.
我说我去 但她想要你去
I offered. She wants you.
这些事件的关联
...a connection between these incidents,
形成了针对费斯特家族的更大阴谋
forming a broader conspiracy against the Fest family.
-护照  -好的
- Passport. - Ja.
这是我第一次过德法边境时
Do you know, this is the first time that I've ever been asked
被要求出示护照
for a passport crossing between Germany and France.
英国护照 马琳森·安东尼
-你从哪过来的  -纽伦堡
- Where are you coming from? - Er, Nuremberg.
你住在纽伦堡吗
Do you live in Nuremberg?
没有 我住在巴黎 你在纽伦堡做什么
Er, no, I live in Paris. What were you doing in Nuremberg?
我和人谈生意
I was visiting someone on business.
-这车是你的吗  -不是 我租的
- Is this your car? - No, it's a rental.
打开后备箱
Open the boot.
请打开行李箱
Open it, please.
这里发生了什么事
What's happening here?
无需担心
Nothing to worry about.
盒子里是什么
What's in the box?
我就是为了这个去纽伦堡的
Ah, so this... is why I was in Nuremberg.
这是
This...
一套杰奎斯的国际象棋
is a Jaques set.
象牙都是禁令前合法获得的
The ivory is all pre-ban.
非常稀有
And it's, er... it's incredibly rare.
我收藏这些东西
I collect these things.
在这等着
Wait here.
-你可以走了  -非常感谢
- You can go. - Thank you very much.
祝你晚上过得愉快
Have a great evening.
谢谢
Thank you.
费斯特枪击案有啥进展
What's the latest on the Fest shooting?
报告才刚出来
Er, the report's literally just come in.
在你电脑上
Should be on your screen now.
一枪爆头 血浆四溅
Single shot to the head. A lot of splatter.
这一枪真准
Bloody good shot.
-这不可能  -怎么了
- No, that can't be right. - What?
三千八百一十五米
3,815 metres.
不可能
But that... that's not possible.
德国人是这么说的
Well, it's what the Germans are saying.
德国人出了名的严谨
And we know how precise the Germans are.
-怎么了  -他们专门为了这事开会
- What's-What's going on? - They've called a meeting about it.
欧斯
Osi. Osi.
我应该参加费斯特案会议
I should be at the Fest meeting.
-之后会给你完整报告  -不行
- You'll get a full briefing afterwards. - No, no, no, no.
我不要完整报告 我熟悉狙击案件
I don't want a full briefing. Snipers is my patch.
-名单不是我写的 比安卡  -等等
- I didn't draw up the names, Bianca. - Well, wait, wait, wait.
- 谁写的 伊莎贝尔吗  -应该是
- Who did? Was it Isabel? - I assume so.
乔丹在里面
Well... Look. Jordan's in there.
乔丹对狙击案件了解多少
Jordan. What does Jordan know about snipers?
我必须进去
I have to be in there.
那是谁啊
Who is that anyway?
沃纳·莱克纳 德国情报部门的
Werner Leckner, German Intelligence.
昨晚在汉堡 柏林和德累斯顿的清真寺
Last night there were arson attacks
有纵火案发生
on mosques in Hamburg, Berlin and Dresden.
德国各地都发生了暴乱
And there's been rioting in different parts of the country.
让人震惊 沃纳
It's obviously very alarming, Werner.
大家都知道 外交大臣和费斯特家族私交甚好
And as you know, the Foreign Secretary was a personal friend of the Fest family.
他非常震惊
He's very shocked.
我们也很震惊 我们可以帮上忙吗
As are we all. What do you need from us?
我们对狙击手的国籍不做猜测
We are not making any assumptions about the nationality of the sniper,
我们正在联系各国
so we are reaching out to all
以寻求协助
our international partners for assistance.
关于那一枪有很多猜测
There's been a lot of speculation about the shot.
你们确认过狙击距离吗
Do you have a confirmed distance?
确认过
Yes, indeed, um...
从开枪的公寓楼
From the apartment block where the shot was taken
到费斯特中枪的医院门口
to the hospital door where Fest was hit is,
有3815米
er... 3,815 metres.
你确定吗
Are you sure about that?
因为狙击步枪最远命中距离的世界纪录是3540米
Because the world record for a confirmed kill with a sniper rifle is 3,540 metres.
记录产生于乌克兰 2023年
Ukraine, 2023.
比安卡·普尔曼　懂枪　让人头疼
-查获到武器了吗  -没有
Did you retrieve the weapon? No.
所以狙击手把枪带走了
Right, so the sniper took it with him.
这是枪击后 过了两分五十二秒
This is the suspect leaving the apartment building,
嫌疑人离开公寓楼的画面
two minutes and 52 seconds after the shot was fired.
等等 枪去哪了
But... er, sorry, where's the rifle?
很显然 他把枪拆解 放进包里了
He broke it down and put it in the bag. Obviously.
能给个尺寸吗
Can we get dimensions, please?
这个包的高度不足六十厘米
The bag is less than 60 centimetres tall.
-所以呢  -塔克50的枪管长度为737毫米
- So? - The Tac-50 barrel is 737 millimetres
这还是同类枪中最短的
and it's the shortest around in this category.
丹尼尔的枪管有一米长
The Denel barrel is a full metre long.
枪不在包里
The-The-The rifle's not in the bag.
要是枪在包里 我们会看到枪管露出来
If it was in the bag, we'd see the barrel poking out.
他把枪藏起来了
He left it behind.
不可能 取证人员在现场没有发现任何武器
No, forensics found no trace of a weapon at the scene.
狙击手有一把能让他在这个距离射击的枪
When a sniper finds a rifle, one that allows him to make a shot at that distance,
这把枪可太牛了
that rifle is a keeper.
他不可能会把枪丢了
He's never going to leave it behind.
也就是说 他把枪带走了
Which means he took it with him.
他要是把枪带走了 那一定装在那个包里
And if he took it with him, then it has to be in that bag.
我没懂 比安卡
I'm not following, Bianca.
可你之前说包不够大
You said the bag isn't big enough?
我的意思是 这枪是定制的
Which means the rifle is bespoke.
枪管由两段组成
The barrel came in two parts.
把枪管分为两段可不简单
A barrel in two parts is the gunmaker's holy grail.
要是膛线有丝毫偏差
If the rifling were out the tiniest fraction,
会严重影响射击 这不可能做到
it would compromise the shot. It's impossible.
有个造枪的人这些年一直尝试这么做
There's a gunmaker who's been trying to do this for years.
他叫诺曼·斯托克
His name is Norman Stoke.
斯托克先生是英国人吗
Is Mr Stoke British?
北爱尔兰人
Northern Irish.
好吧
Well...
那暂时也算是英国人吧
I suppose they count as British, for now.
我们有斯托克先生的位置信息吗
Do we know where Mr Stoke is?
要派特别行动组抓他吗
Can we get Special Branch to scoop him up?
2018年斯德哥尔摩刺杀案后 他就一直在逃
He's been on the run since the Stockholm assassination in 2018.
-可惜了  -不过我有一个线人
- How unfortunate. - But I have an asset.
我一定能找到他
I know I can find him.
这对我们有什么帮助
What good would that do us?
造枪的人造好枪
Oh, well, gunmaker makes gun.
会把枪卖给杀手
Gunmaker sells gun to assassin.
-大胆的推断  -但算是条线索
- Highly speculative. - It is a lead, however.
坦白说 我们现在也没太多线索
And, to be frank, we don't have many of those.
巴黎  法国
航站楼
-你好  -你好
- Bonjour. - Bonjour.
去北站
比安卡 你留一下
Bianca. A moment, please.
德国人来向我们求助 总让我感到受宠若惊
It's always flattering when the Germans come asking for our expertise.
虽然如果造枪者真是英国人 可能会有些尴尬
Although it would be a little embarrassing if the gunmaker turns out to be British.
诺曼·斯托克 到底是何许人
Who exactly is this Norman Stoke?
斯托克上世纪八十年代开始
Stoke started making machine-guns
为效忠英国的北爱尔兰准军事团体制造机枪
for loyalist paramilitaries back in the '80s in East Belfast.
诺曼和他兄弟拉里 杀了十多个无辜的天主教平民
Norman and his brother Larry, killed more than a dozen innocent Catholic civilians.
拉里最终被抓 坐了牢
Larry was eventually caught and went to prison
但根据和平协议 他之后获释了
but was released under the peace agreement.
他现在是贩毒团伙的打手
Er, he's now an enforcer for a gang of drug dealers.
在这期间 诺曼的造枪技艺愈发精湛
Norman, meanwhile, perfected his craft
制造了斯德哥尔摩刺杀事件中的枪
and made the gun used in the Stockholm assassination.
要怎么找到诺曼·斯托克
How would you go about finding Norman Stoke?
我在贝尔法斯特有个线人
I have an asset in Belfast.
代号麻雀
Codename Sparrow.
我知道你很优秀 比安卡
I've heard good things about you, Bianca.
别让我失望
Don't let me down.
嗯
Yeah.
提示
此设备将替换操作系统
取消
替换
脚本运行中...
暗核
暗核浏览器
聊天
进入聊天室
用户名
密码
取消
登录
慕尼黑尾款
正在与客户确认 请稍候
在等
慕尼黑尾款
正在与客户确认 请稍候
-喂  -喂
- Hey. - Hey.
贝尔法斯特  北爱尔兰
你貌似在机场
You look like you're at an airport.
-对 抱歉  -可是家长会怎么办
- Yeah, sorry. - But what about parents' evening?
看来你去不了了
So, I'm assuming you're not coming?
临时有事
It's a last-minute thing.
她这学期真的很努力
You know, she's really worked her socks off this term.
我知道 我也很难过 但没办法
I know, I know. I feel awful about it. There was nothing I could do.
你要不亲口和她说
Well, you could try telling her yourself?
保罗 不行 我刚到贝尔法斯特
Paul, I can't, I can't. I-I've just got to Belfast
我已经开会迟到了
and I'm-I'm already late for a meeting.
-好吧  -你能代我去吗
- Right, OK. - Can you do it, please?
-行  -我会尽量赶最晚一班航班回来
- OK. - Look, I will try my best to get on the last flight.
好吗
OK.OK?
-抱歉  -好吧 再见
- I'm sorry. - Alright, bye, bye.
再见
OK, bye.
慕尼黑尾款
正在与客户确认 请稍候
在等
预计什么时候？
慕尼黑尾款
正在与客户确认 请稍候
在等
预计什么时候？
24小时内到账
来自CRTVDSTRYR*1908$的1条新消息
非常欣赏你的工作 我们有一个项目 相信你会感兴趣 报酬极为丰厚
需要我干什么？
不在这聊 能见面吗?
我不见客户
非常欣赏你的工作 我们有一个项目 相信你会感兴趣 报酬极为丰厚
需要我干什么？
不在这聊 能见面吗?
我不见客户
需要我干什么？
不在这聊 能见面吗?
我不见客户
开价1千万 另有额外奖金 见面吗?
线下见面费为100万 一半定金 一半见面后付清　双方都可以选择后续不合作 但需要保证支付给我100万见面费
不在这聊 能见面吗?
我不见客户
开价1千万 另有额外奖金 见面吗?
时间地点？
收到定金后会提供详细信息
我看到你的号码 差点脑溢血
When I saw your number, I almost had a stroke.
我以为我再也不用见到你了
Thought I'd seen the last of you.
好久不见
It has been a long time.
最近怎么样
How've you been?
-你想怎么样 娜丁  -家里都好吗
- What do you want, Nadine? - How's the family?
别牵扯到我的家人
Leave my family out of it.
拉里要是知道我和你说话 会杀了我
If Larry knew who I was talking to, he'd kill me.
好了 非常感谢
There you go. Thanks ever so much.
欢迎下次再来
Do come back and see us.
谢谢
Have a good day.
你没暴露吧
But you're being careful?
-你记得协议吗  -记得
- You remember the protocols? - Yes.
很好
Good.
那你就不需要担心什么了
Then there's nothing for you to worry about.
拉里上一次联系他弟弟诺曼是什么时候
When was the last time Larry spoke to his brother, Norman?
诺曼失踪前
Not since he disappeared.
艾莉森 你没在骗我吧
Are you telling me the truth, Alison?
我知道他们兄弟俩关系很好 我现在要找诺曼
I know the brothers are close and I need to find Norman now.
不关我的事
Not my problem.
和你关系很大
It's very much your problem,
因为如果你不帮我找到诺曼
because if you don't help me find Norman,
你会继续蹲监狱
you'll go back to prison.
你结婚了吗
Are you married?
-没有  -有小孩吗
- No. - Children?
-没有  -职场女强人
- Nope. - Career woman.
显而易见
It's written all over you.
你要是结了婚 就会知道男人都有自己的小秘密
If you had a husband, you'd know men have their little secrets.
我想窥探一下这个小秘密
Well, this is a little secret I want in on.
你得告诉我诺曼现在在哪
I need you to find out where Norman is today.
我不能直接问拉里
I can't just ask Larry out the blue.
他会起疑 我得旁敲侧击
He'll be suspicious. I'd have to work up to it.
你有我的号码
You've got my number.
我今晚等你的消息
I expect to hear from you tonight.
我可以走了吗
Can I go now?
没人会阻拦
It's a free country.
准备就绪
已支付见面费定金
我是艾莉森 请留言
This is Alison. Leave a message.
艾莉森 我是娜丁
Alison, it's Nadine.
我没收到你的消息 我非常失望 请打电话给我
I haven't heard from you and I'm very disappointed. Call me.
娜丁
Nadine?
哦 办公室里的外号
Oh, office in-joke.
宝贝 对不起
Look, baby, I'm so sorry.
家长会的事 我真的对不起你
You know, about parents' evening. I really am.
梅拉伦湖  瑞典
别回头
Don't turn around.
你是一个人来的吗
Did you come alone?
对 我按照你的要求
Yes, I followed your instructions to the letter.
目标是谁
Who's the target?
乌勒·达格·查尔斯 乌达查
Ulle Dag Charles. UDC.
你能办到吗
Can you get to him?
价格会很高
It'll cost.
我开价一千万美元
I mentioned a guide price of ten million dollars.
这个数乘以十 我们才有得谈
Multiply that by ten and then perhaps we can have a conversation.
这次谈话真费钱
That's a very expensive conversation.
一半定金 一半尾款
Half on commission, half on completion.
所有合理的费用都由你们承担
All reasonable expenses paid.
我得跟同事商量一下
Well, I'd have to consult my colleagues about that.
在吗
Hello?
艾莉森 我是娜丁 你昨晚应该给我打电话的
Alison, it's Nadine. You were supposed to call me last night.
快联系我
I need to hear from you.
把艾莉森女儿艾玛的资料 统统给我找出来
Er, get me everything we have on Alison's daughter, Emma.
-可以吗  -好 我来找
- Yeah? - Copy. Yeah, yeah. On it.
德国联邦情报局认为
The BND believe, er...
德国联邦情报局推测 狙击手以为自己前一晚
The BND believe our sniper thought he'd find Manfred
能在费斯特公司找到曼弗雷德
at the Fest Und Fest Unternehme offices the night before.
但曼弗雷德不在公司 于是他射伤了埃利亚斯
But Manfred wasn't there so he shot his son, Elias.
曼弗雷德才是真正的目标
Manfred was always the real target.
埃利亚斯是诱饵 引诱曼弗雷德去医院
Elias was used as bait to lure Manfred to the hospital.
这需要大量的前期准备
That would take a lot of pre-planning.
都是计划好的
Well, all planning is pre.
贝尔法斯特那边怎么样了
How did Belfast go?
线人不配合我
My asset isn't cooperating.
我们可能得用点特殊手段
I think we have to get creative on this one.
她有个女儿 叫艾玛
She has a daughter, Emma.
在伦敦上学
A student in London.
参与激进左派团体
Involved in a radical leftist group.
我大概能猜到你要干嘛
I think I can see where you're going with this.
我们批准这种行动必须非常谨慎
We have to be very careful about sanctioning this kind of operation.
乌达查
UDC! UDC! UDC! UDC!
我们要什么 资金的真相
What do we want?! The truth about money!
我们什么时候要 现在
When do we want it? Now!
乌达查
UDC! UDC! UDC!
资流可以使资金流动透明
River's here to make it clear!
你们不能在这里洗钱
You can't wash your money here!
乌达查
UDC! UDC! UDC! UDC!
那个披着粉色围巾的
Yep, that's her in the pink scarf.
要等她做出出格举动吗
Do I have to wait for her to act up?
不用 直接行动
No. Just go get her.
没问题
Fine by me.
女士 你妨碍了公共交通
Miss, you're causing an obstruction in a public highway.
如果你不马上起身离开 我就逮捕你
If you do not get up and move right now, you're liable for arrest.
你干嘛不做点有意义的事
Why don't you go and do something useful
有本事你去逮捕那些有钱有权的人啊
like arrest the fat cats...
你们不能在这里洗钱
You can't wash your money here!
我不是在恐吓你 女士
I'm not threatening you, miss.
你该站在我的角度想想
Well, OK, well you should try being where I am...
对我而言 这就是恐吓
That's a threat. It's a threat to me.
我已经很通情达理了
I'm being reasonable.
我没像你一样提高嗓门
I'm not raising my voice in the way that you are.
我不在乎你们的法律 我不在乎
I don't care about your law, I don't care!
不用说了 逮捕他们
Right, that's enough. Have 'em up. Thank you!
别碰我 你们这些走狗
Get your hands off me, lackey!
街道属于谁 属于我们
Whose streets?! Our streets!...
艾玛 你摊上大事了
You're in very serious trouble, Emma.
你摊上大事了
You're in very serious trouble.
有四位证人看到你向警察丢瓶子
We have four witnesses who saw you throw the bottle at the police officer.
有四位证人
We got four witnesses
看到你向警察丢瓶子
who saw you throw the bottle at the police officer.
什么瓶子
What bottle?
你在说些什么 没人丢东西
What are you talking about? Nobody was throwing anything.
你甚至不关心那个警察
You didn't even ask about the officer.
-她伤得很重  -我没扔瓶子
- She was badly hurt. - I didn't throw any bottle.
那个警察的右眼会失明
The officer's gonna lose her right eye.
她的右眼会失明 你却这么冷漠
She's gonna lose her right eye, since you didn't ask.
她只是一个年轻女性
Just a young woman,
在履行她的职责
doing her job.
艾玛 你作何感想
How's that make you feel, Emma?
都是你编的
You're making this up.
滚一边去
So fuck right off.
我要见律师
And I want a solicitor.
我有权见律师
I have a right to a solicitor.
你可以给你母亲打电话
You can call your mother.
这边
This way, please.
-别碰我  -进去
- Fuck off me! - Get in there.
我的律师呢
Where's my solicitor?!
我的律师呢 这样做是违法的
Where's my solicitor?! This is illegal!
加的斯  西班牙
你怎么回来了
天啊
Oh, my God!
我以为你下周才回来
I wasn't expecting you until next week.
那就会错过卡利托斯的生日 没门儿
What and miss Carlito's birthday? Not happening.
-说吧  -我看到她时 就是这样了
- Talk to me. - She was like this when I found her.
她还没死 我已经叫了救护人员
She's still alive. I've called the paramedics.
请在提示音后留言
"At the tone, please record your message."
比安卡
Bianca,
你让我抓的学生出了大问题
we've got a serious problem with your student.
-怎么回事  -她晕倒了
- What the fuck is going on? - She collapsed.
医护人员说是心脏病 已经稳定住了
They think it's a cardiac issue. They've stabilised her.
她能挺住
They think she's gonna make it.
我是随行警察
I'm the accompanying officer.
艾玛 坚持住
Emma. Hang on, OK?
你会没事的
You're gonna be alright.
进入聊天室
用户名
密码
取消
登录
怎么了
What's happening?
她没心跳了
She's arrested.
-我要用除颤器  -我来帮忙
- I'm gonna shock her. - Let me help.
充电
Charging.
站远点 电击
Stand clear! Shocking.
24小时查询账户
预计什么时候？
未收到付款
慕尼黑的375万欧元仍未支付
去你
妈的